<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence | Mohan Nataraj</title>
    <link>https://mohanataraj.github.io/tags/artificial-intelligence/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://mohanataraj.github.io/tags/artificial-intelligence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Artificial Intelligence</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 19:36:51 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://mohanataraj.github.io/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_box_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://mohanataraj.github.io/tags/artificial-intelligence/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dude you broke the future</title>
      <link>https://mohanataraj.github.io/post/dudeyoubrokethefuture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 19:36:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mohanataraj.github.io/post/dudeyoubrokethefuture/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is pretty cool talk by Charles Stross, given at &lt;strong&gt;Chaos Computer Club&lt;/strong&gt; congression this talk reflects my opinion or views on current world of corporates, startups, artificial intelligence (referred by speaker as corporate AI and computerized AI) and one ridiculed CEO or lets say more than one [:P]. You can also find reason&amp;rsquo;s on why I quit facebook or hated it in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The talk starts by saying on how prediction 3 centuries back or even a century back was possible to do accurately. Which infact reminds me of what my astrologer threw at me when I asked him where I will exactly be in 5 years [😄], yep a typical &lt;strong&gt;South Indian boy&lt;/strong&gt;. Further the speaker talks about Artificial Intelligence singularity (computerized), infact you can giggle on when the speaker says @ 7:30 &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;if we created an AI equivalent of human mind it would be sitting on a couch and watching super bowl all day&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;, I&amp;rsquo;m sure to say this is one of the least obnoxious way anyone can put it knowing what we human&amp;rsquo;s are capable of doing or the way we live in 21&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;st&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; century.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To continue on the speaker says &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;AI as self optimizing tool which defy human comprehension&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;, which is quite absolutely right, and while the comparison of airplane to seagull makes us want to giggle, we can also wonder if our education system &amp;amp; professor&amp;rsquo;s are doing good enough to produce skillful people or are we just about the grades ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, continuing on the next statement that caught my attention when the speaker says &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;history is useful for so much more than that&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; funny on how forget our past in speaker&amp;rsquo;s words &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;our personal memory don&amp;rsquo;t span very long at all&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;, haha! in fact, every 5 year&amp;rsquo;s we vote. [:D]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The speaker further goes on to talk about paper clip maximizer theory of artificial intelligence and one of the CEO that supports it. Which to me seems funny on how people see things especially some the most renowned CEO&amp;rsquo;s. Just WOW!!! The speakers quirky comments are quite joyful and his correlation to corporations and governmental organization are so damn true.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While I can go on for quite a bit about this talk. I would like to keep the writing short and let you watch the video. This is more of an opinionated talk and is very entertaining. The speaker not so surprisingly also talks about the corporations like Facebook - its role in the society and developers building app&amp;rsquo;s that gets people addicted to them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The speaker Charles Stross quite greatly articulates my views and reasons why I&amp;rsquo;m not on &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;facebook&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; and as well don&amp;rsquo;t own a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;smart phone&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; anymore. It&amp;rsquo;s been almost a year and yep I am &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;that 90&amp;rsquo;s kid&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; it&amp;rsquo;s been great spending more time improving myself than being socially obsessed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you enjoy this video and get alot to learn. You have any comments, opinions or anything to discuss or want to know you can comment below or mail me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; Need to update this again &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
