<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mohan Nataraj</title>
    <link>https://binarybot.github.io/authors/mohan-nataraj/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mohan Nataraj</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 23:13:20 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://binarybot.github.io/authors/mohan-nataraj/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mind Body Soul</title>
      <link>https://binarybot.github.io/post/mind-body-soul/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 23:13:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarybot.github.io/post/mind-body-soul/</guid>
      <description>Summary : Mind, body and soul the three aspect of life that I balance to keep myself happy and engaging. Also will I ever stop studying Mathematics &amp;amp; Science in my life ? Is love necessary part of our life, if so which one does it hold dear to [mind, body or soul] while dearly wait for my mysterious her. Stay connected, people say they get bored, while I think there are so many open problems in so many fields or areas of education to be solved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dude you broke the future</title>
      <link>https://binarybot.github.io/post/dudeyoubrokethefuture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 19:36:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarybot.github.io/post/dudeyoubrokethefuture/</guid>
      <description>This is pretty cool talk by Charles Stross, given at Chaos Computer Club congression this talk reflects my opinion or views on current world of corporates, startups, artificial intelligence (referred by speaker as corporate AI and computerized AI) and one ridiculed CEO or lets say more than one [:P]. You can also find reason&amp;rsquo;s on why I quit facebook or hated it in the first place.
The talk starts by saying on how prediction 3 centuries back or even a century back was possible to do accurately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Childhood Puzzle Revealed</title>
      <link>https://binarybot.github.io/post/childhoodpuzzelrevealed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 19:25:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://binarybot.github.io/post/childhoodpuzzelrevealed/</guid>
      <description>Whilst &amp;ldquo;Bridges&amp;rdquo; are built to span through obstacles, the preceding statement was quite erring in the city of Königsberg in Prussia (now Kaliningrad, Russia) during the 18th century. Here we talk about the inception of Graph Theory, it&amp;rsquo;s application to the real world problems and a famous puzzle asked during my childhood. The blog also contain a pretty good talk given by a math student below in Chaos Computer Club congression.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>